Guide to the Athletics and Recreation Department records, 1890-2009 RG0054
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Athletics and Recreation Department records
1890-2011
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
George Washington University. Athletics Dept.
RG0054
133.5 Linear Feet
Materials in this collection include media guides, films, brochures, videotapes, uniforms, artifacts, football programs, statistics, magazines, photographs, trophies, newsletters, and news releases. They range in date from 1907-2005, and were transferred to the University Archives by the Director of the Department of Athletics.
Restrictions on Access
Some records may be restricted.
Acquisition Information
Materials acquired through transfers from the Athletics and Recreation Department.
Historical or Biographical Note
Organized athletics have been a part of The George Washington University since the late nineteenth century. The Department of Athletics and Recreation is headed by a Director of Athletics, who oversees the following units: Administration, Academic Support, Recreational Sports, Athletics Communications (sports information and community outreach), Sports Medicine, Baseball, Basketball (men's and women's), Rowing (crew), Cross Country, Golf, Gymnastics, Lacrosse (women's), Soccer (men's and women's), Softball (women's), Squash (men's and women's), Swimming & Diving, Tennis (men's and women's), Volleyball, Water Polo (men's and women's). Before 1988 their were separate Departments for men and women's athletics. The Director of Athletics reports to the Vice President for Student and Academic Support Services. The Department publishes annual media guides for varsity sports.
N.B. This history note was written in 2005
Collection Scope and Content
Materials in this collection include media guides, films, brochures, videotapes, uniforms, artifacts, football programs, statistics, magazines, photographs, trophies, newsletters, and news releases. They range in date from 1907-2011, and were transferred to the University Archives by the Director of the Department of Athletics.
Formerly RG 6.4.2; there is no series 15.
Collection Organization
Organized into forty-three series: George Washington sports information collection; Basketball films; Guides, programs, notebooks, and Hatchets; Newspaper clippings; Videotapes; Uniforms; Certificate and photograph; Newspaper clippings; Programs, guides, posters, profiles, and shirt; Football team photographs; Women's rifle club collection; Trophies; Program and ticket; Jump rope; William Reinhart, papers; Banners; Cheerleader uniforms; Bill Ryan football memorabilia; Letterman's sweaters; Basketball ephemera; Football ponchos; Colonials Sports News; Intramural sports handbooks; Colonial Cager newspaper; Athletic uniforms and George mascot costume; George mascot heads and costumes; Athletic uniforms and artifacts; Blanket, sweater, and jersey; Sports media guides; Football programs; Basketball memorabilia; Shirts; Basketball memorabilia; Women's volleyball videotapes; Basketball memorabilia; Jerseys, programs, letter, and magazine; Departmental files; videotapes; athletic uniforms and memorabilia; basketball game programs and media guides; sports media guides, posters, basketball programs and jerseys.
Lacrosse; Gymnastics; Softball; Soccer; Swimming; Squash rackets (Game); Photographs; Foggy Bottom (Washington, D.C.); Diving; Washington (D.C.); Football; Water polo; Cross-country running; Golf -- Washington (D.C.); Basketball; Rowing; Baseball; Volleyball; Tennis; Jarvis, Mike; George Washington University; Reinhart, William Jennings Bryan; Pixlee, James; Leemans, Alphonse "Tuffy"
- George Washington sports information collection, 1930-1993; RG0054 Series 1; 15 Linear feet (Box 6, Box 5, Box 11, Box 8, Box 10, Box 7, Box 9, Box 2, Box 1, Box 4, Box 3)
  Scope and Contents note
  This series consists football media guides and game statistics, brochures, meeting minutes, news letters, magazines, scrapbooks, film, videotape, memorabilia, and news clippings. Subjects include: football, wrestling, rifle, sports clubs, Colonials, Inc. (a booster club), and women's athletics.
  They range in date from 1930-93, and were transferred to the University Archives by the Director of the Department of Athletics in 1996.
  Formerly ACC#552, formerly RG6.4
  - Football - Records, Coaches, Players, 1890-1966 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Football - 1st night game, 10/16/1930 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Football - Game Statistics, 1932 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Football - Game Statistics, 1933 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Football - Game Statistics, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Football - Game Statistics, 1935 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Football - Game Statistics, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Football - Game Statistics, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Football - West Virginia game, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Football - Game Statisitcs, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Football - Roster and Schedule, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Football - Roster, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Football - Game Statistics, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Football - Game Statistics and script for radio show, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Football - Game Statistics, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Football - Game Statistics, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Football - Game Statistics, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Football - Game Statistics, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Football - Conference Statistics, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Football - Game Statistics, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Football - Game Statistics and Press Releases, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Football - Game Statistics, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Football - Game Statistics, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Football - Sun Bowl Game, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Football - Sun Bowl Game - Statistics and play-by-play log, 01/01/1957 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Football - Game Statistics, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Football - Game Statistics and play-by-play logs, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Football - Game Statistics and play-by-play logs, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Football - Game Statistics and play-by-play logs, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Football - Game Statistics and play-by-play logs, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Football - Southern Conference Statistics, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Football - Game Statistics and play-by-play logs, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Football - Game Statistics and play-by-play logs [1/2], 1963 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Football - Game Statistics and play-by-play logs [2/2], 1963 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Football - Game Statistics and play-by-play logs, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Football - Game Statistics and play-by-play logs, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Football - Alumni game, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Football - Game Statistics and play-by-play logs, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Football - Frosh player information, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Football - Statistics for GW, Southern Conference and NCAA, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Football - Davidson game, 09/17/1966 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Football - Virginia Tech game, 09/24/1966 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Football - William and Mary game, 10/01/1966 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Football - The Citadel game, 10/08/1966 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Football - East Carolina game, 10/15/1966 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Football - V.M.I. game, 10/22/1966 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Football - Fuman game, 10/29/1966 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Football - Army game, 11/05/1966 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Football - University of West Virginia game, 11/12/1966 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Football - Villanova game, 11/24/1966 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Football - Media Guide, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    General note
    3 copies
  - Football - Media Guide, 1941 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    2 copies
  - Football - Media Guide, 1942 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Football - Media Guide, 1950 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Football - Media Guide, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Football - Media Guide, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Football - Media Guide, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Football - Media Guide, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Football - Media Guide, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Football - Media Guide, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Football - Media Guide, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Football - NCAA Media Guide, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Football - Media Guide, 1961-1962 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    2 copies 1962; 1 copy 1961
  - Football - Media Guide, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Football - Media Guide, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Football - Media Guide, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    4 copies
  - Football - Media Guide, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Football - Game film, Kentucky, 1951 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    Added via transfer, Sept. 2004
  - Football - Game film- William and Mary (n.d.) and Sun Bowl, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Football - Game film, Sun Bowl, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    Added via transfer Sept. 2004
  - Football - Game films, unidentified, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Football - Game films, Furman, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Football - Game films, Hollan-Haught, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Football - Game films, Furman, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Football - Game films, The Citadel, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Football - Game films, East Carolina [1/2], 1966 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Football - Game films, East Carolina [2/2], 1966 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Football - Game films, unidentified, undated (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Football - Game films, unidentified, undated (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Men's rifle team, 1937-1938 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    With results from 1909 to 1937
  - Men's rifle team, 1950-1955 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Men's rifle team, 1963-1964 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Men's rifle team, 1965-1966 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Men's rifle team, 1967-1968 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Men's rifle team, 1968-1969 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Men's rifle team, 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Men's rifle team, 1970-1972 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Wrestling team, 1968-1969 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Wrestling team, 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Wrestling team, 1970-1971 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Wrestling team, 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Wrestling team, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Wrestling team, 1973-1974 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Wrestling team, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Wrestling team, 1975-1976 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Wrestling team, 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Wrestling team, 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Wrestling team, 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Wrestling team, 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Wrestling team, 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Wrestling team, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Wrestling team, 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Wrestling team, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Wrestling team, 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Wrestling team, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Wrestling team [1/2], 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Wrestling team [2/2], 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Wrestling team [1/2], 1987-1988 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Wrestling team [2/2], 1987-1988 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Wrestling team [1/2], 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Wrestling team [2/2], 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Sports Clubs - General, 1963-1970 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Sports Clubs - Caving Club (GW Grotto Club), 1967-1970 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Sports Clubs - Club Football, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Sports Clubs - Cricket Club, 1969-1971 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Sports Clubs - Diving Club, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Sports Clubs - Ice Hockey Club, 1973-1974 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Sports Clubs - Lacrosse Club, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Sports Clubs - Outing Club, 1966-1967 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Sports Clubs - Parachute Club, 1969-1972 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Sports Clubs - Rugby Club, 1967-1971 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Sports Clubs - Sailing Club, 1967-1968 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Sports Clubs - Ski Club, 1969-1971 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Sports Clubs - Soccer Club, 1967-1968 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Sports Clubs - Wrestling Club, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Atlantic 10 conference information, 1987-1988 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Atlantic 10 conference information, 1989-1990 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Academic achievement statistics, 1987-1988 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Academic All-American nominees, 1985-1993 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Francis Field, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 51)
    Also includes photos
  - Players - Holloran, Mike (baseball and football photos and certificates), 1965 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Colonials, Inc. - Constitution and By-Laws, undated (Box 3, Folder 53)
    Colonials, Inc. was an athletics booster club
  - Colonials, Inc., 1971 (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - Colonials, Inc., 1972 (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - Colonials, Inc., 1973 (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - Colonials, Inc., 1974 (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - Colonials, Inc., 1975 (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - Colonials, Inc., 1976 (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - Colonials, Inc., 1977 (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - Colonials, Inc., 1978 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Colonials, Inc. - sports awards dinner, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Colonials, Inc., 1979 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Colonials, Inc., - memberships, 1979-1980 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Colonials, Inc., 1980 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Colonials, Inc., 1981-1982 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Colonials, Inc., 1982-1983 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Colonials, Inc. - membership, 1982-1983 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Colonials, Inc. - sports award dinner, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Colonials, Inc., 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Colonials, Inc. - membership, 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Colonials, Inc., 1984-1985 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Colonials, Inc. - sports award dinner, 1984-1985 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Colonials, Inc., 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Colonials, Inc. - sports award dinner, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Colonials, Inc. - mailing lists, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Colonials, Inc., 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Colonials, Inc. - membership, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Colonials, Inc. - bank deposits, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Colonials, Inc., 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Colonials, Inc., 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Colonials, Inc. - Colonial Club Cruise, 10/1988 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Colonial Basketball magazine, vol. 1, 1982-1983 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Colonial Basketball magazine, vol. 2, 1982-1983 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Colonial Illustrated magazine, vol. 3, 1982-1983 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Colonial Illustrated magazine, vol. 4, 1982-1983 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Colonial Illustrated magazine, vol. 5, 1982-1983 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Colonial Illustrated magazine, vol. 1, 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Colonial Illustrated magazine, vol. 2, 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Colonial Illustrated magazine, vol. 3, 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Colonial Illustrated magazine, vol. 4, 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Colonial Illustrated magazine, vol. 5, 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Colonial Illustrated magazine, vol. 1, 1984-1985 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Colonial Illustrated magazine, vol. 2, 1984-1985 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Colonial Illustrated magazine, vol. 3, 1984-1985 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Colonial Illustrated magazine, vol. 4, 1984-1985 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Colonial Illustrated magazine, vol. 5, 1984-1985 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Colonial Cager magazine, vol. 1, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Colonial Cager magazine, vol. 3, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Colonial Cager magazine, vol. 4, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Colonial Cager magazine, vol. 1, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Colonial Cager magazine, vol. 2, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Colonial Cager magazine, vol. 3, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Colonial Cager magazine, vol. 4, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Colonial Cager magazine, vol. 1, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Colonial Cager magazine, vol. 2, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Athletic Federation of College Women (AFCW) Conferences, 1935-1942 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - AFCWC [Athletic Federation of College Women] Conference Procedings, 1964-1968 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Eastern Association of Intercollegiate Athletics for Women - Directory, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Intramural Board, 1935-1936 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Intramural Board, 1936-1937 (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Intramural Board, 1937-1938 (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Intramural Board, 1938-1939 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Intramural Board, 1939-1940 (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Intramural Board, 1940-1941 (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Intramural Board, 1941-1942 (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Intramural Board, 1942-1943 (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Intramural Board, 1944-1945 (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Intramural Board, 1945-1946 (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - Inter-Sorority Athletic Board (ISAB) - Constitution, 1950 ca.-1960 -- --ca. (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - [Inter-Sorority Athletic Board] ISAB, 1949-1950 (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - [Inter-Sorority Athletic Board] ISAB, 1952-1953 (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - [Inter-Sorority Athletic Board] ISAB, 1953-1954 (Box 4, Folder 63)
  - [Inter-Sorority Athletic Board] ISAB, 1954-1955 (Box 4, Folder 64)
  - [Inter-Sorority Athletic Board] ISAB, 1955-1956 (Box 4, Folder 65)
  - [Inter-Sorority Athletic Board] ISAB, 1956-1957 (Box 4, Folder 66)
  - [Inter-Sorority Athletic Board] ISAB, 1957-1958 (Box 4, Folder 67)
  - [Inter-Sorority Athletic Board] ISAB, 1966-1970 (Box 4, Folder 68)
  - Women's Athletic Association (WAA) - Constitutions, 1940 ca.-1960 -- --ca. (Box 4, Folder 69)
  - [Women's Athletic Association] WAA - Points System, 1941-1955 (Box 4, Folder 70)
  - [Women's Athletic Association] WAA - List of Presdients and By-Laws, undated (Box 4, Folder 71)
  - [Women's Athletic Association] WAA, 1928 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Women's Recreational Association (WRA), 1941-1942 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - [Women's Athletic Association] WAA - News Clippings, 1942-1943 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - [Women's Athletic Association] WAA, 1945-1946 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - [Women's Recreational Association] WRA, 1947-1948 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - [Women's Recreational Association] WRA, 1948-1949 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - [Women's Recreational Association] WRA, 1949-1950 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - [Women's Recreational Association] WRA, 1950-1951 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - [Women's Recreational Association] WRA, 1951-1952 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - [Women's Recreational Association] WRA, 1952-1953 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - [Women's Recreational Association] WRA -Sports Day, 1952-1953 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - [Women's Recreational Association] WRA, 1953-1954 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - [Women's Recreational Association] WRA - Budget Ledger, 1949-1956 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - [Women's Athletic Association] WAA - Meeting Minutes, 1954-1955 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - AFCW [Athletic Federation of College Women] - National Convention, 1955 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - [Women's Athletic Association] WAA, 1955-1956 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - [Women's Athletic Association] WAA - Meeting Minutes, 1955-1956 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - AFCW [Athletic Federation of College Women], 1955-1956 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - [Women's Athletic Association] WAA - Duties of Sports Managers, 1955 ca. (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - [Women's Athletic Association] WAA, 1956-1957 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - [Women's Athletic Association] WAA - Meeting Minutes, 1956-1957 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - [Women's Athletic Association] WAA, 1957-1958 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - [Women's Athletic Association] WAA - Meeting Minutes, 1957-1958 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - [Women's Athletic Association] WAA, 1958-1959 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - [Women's Athletic Association] WAA - Meeting Minutes, 1958-1959 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - [Women's Athletic Association] WAA, 1959-1960 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - [Women's Athletic Association] WAA - Sports Day, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - [Women's Athletic Association] WAA, 1960-1961 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - [Women's Athletic Association] WAA, 1961-1962 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - [Women's Athletic Association] WAA - Basketball Report, 1962-1963 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - [Women's Athletic Association] WAA - Basketball Report, 1963-1964 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - [Women's Athletic Association] WAA, 1964-1965 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - [Women's Athletic Association] WAA, 1965-1966 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - [Women's Athletic Association] WAA, 1966-1967 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - [Women's Recreational Association] WRA - Newsletter, 1966-1969 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - [Women's Recreational Association] WRA - Surveys of interest, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - National Association for Physical Education of college women - Amy Morris Homas lectures, 1967-1969 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - [Women's Athletic Association] WAA, 1967-1968 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - [Women's Athletic Association] WAA, 1968-1969 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - [Women's Athletic Association] WAA, 1969-1970 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Women's badminton, 1978-1979 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Women's badminton - rosters, 1978-1979 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Women's badminton, 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Women's badminton, 1981-1982 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Women's badminton, 1982-1983 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Women's badminton, 1983-1984 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Women's badminton, 1984-1985 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Women's badminton, 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Women's badminton - results, 1986-1987 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Women's badminton schedule/roster, 1986-1987 (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Women's badminton, 1987-1988 (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Women's badminton - results, 1988-1989 (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Women's badminton - schedule/roster, 1988-1989 (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - Sports publicity log book, 1959-1963 (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - Scrapbooks of news clippings and programs - Orchesis dance, WAA, rifle, tennis, swimming, canoeing, field hockey, basketball, equestrian, 10/1938-04/1940 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Scrapbooks of news clippings and programs - Dance, horse shows, sports days, 1931-1939 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Scrapbooks of news clippings and programs - WAA, swimming, basketball, equestrian, rifle, tennis, dance, sports days, 1931-1935 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Scrapbooks of news clippings and programs - Basketball (mainly), baseball, tennis, crew, 1969-1972 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Scrapbooks of news clippings and programs - Basketball (mainly), baseball, crew, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Scrapbooks of news clippings and programs - Basketball (mainly), baseball, soccer, 1973-1975 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Scrapbooks of news clippings and programs - Basketball (mainly), baseball, tennis, 1975-1976 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Scrapbooks of news clippings and programs - Basketball (mainly), baseball, crew, soccer, 1976-1978 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Scrapbooks of news clippings and programs - Basketball (mainly), baseball, 1978-1980 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Scrapbooks of news clippings and programs - Basketball (mainly), baseball, tennis, soccer, 1980-1982 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - News clips and transcripts from televison broadcasts dealing with men's basketball team, 1991-1993 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    Many articles related to the "Sweet 16" appearance in 1993
  - Basketball film - GW vs. Villanova [1/4], 1979-1980 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Basketball film - GW vs. Villanova [2/4], 1979-1980 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Basketball film - GW vs. Villanova [3/4], 1979-1980 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Basketball film - GW vs. Villanova [4/4], 1979-1980 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Basketball film - GW vs. Maryland [1/4], undated (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Basketball film - GW vs. Maryland [2/4], undated (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Basketball film - GW vs. Maryland [3/4], undated (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Basketball film - GW vs. Maryland [4/4], undated (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Basketball videotape - Mike Brown, 12/1984 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    u-matic tape
  - Basketball film - sports spot, Mike Brown, undated (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Basketball videotape - sports spot [1/2], undated (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Basketball videotape - sports spot [2/2], undated (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Basketball videotape - U. of Rhode Island game, first half, undated (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Basketball videotape - U. of Rhode Island game, second half, undated (Box 9, Folder 2)